http://www.soyringconsulting.com/privacy-policy

Not Sure Which Services
You Need Help With?
Let us help you achieve the results you are looking for.
FREE WHITE PAPER
Managing Bottlenecks to Increase Perioperative Efficiency
Ready to Get Started
With Soyring?
Let us help you achieve the results you are looking for.
FREE WHITE PAPER
Managing Bottlenecks to Increase Perioperative Efficiency
Privacy Policy
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.soyringconsulting.com and applies solely to information collected by this website, owned by Soyring Consulting, Inc., located at 880 21st Avenue North, St. Petersburg, FL, USA.
Soyring Consulting (Soyring) is sensitive to the privacy of those who visit our website. We recognize the need for appropriate protections and management of your personal information that is provided to us via this website. Soyring has therefore established this privacy policy to assist you in understanding what information we collect from you and how that information is used.
Please read this privacy policy carefully. By accessing this website, you are indicating that you acknowledge and agree to the terms and conditions set forth in this privacy policy.
General
Soyring respects the privacy of every individual who visits www.soyringconsulting.com. Soyring focuses on providing you with timely and insightful industry information gathered from our team of experienced medical consultants. Our information details many of the issues facing your facility, or department and provides actionable tips for solving them.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
In general, you can visit the Soyring website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share this information with any third-party outside of our organization without your permission.
We may contact you via email in the future to tell you about service offerings. If you receive an email from us, it is because you have had some contact with our company. Be assured that in receiving information from us, we will not sell, share, or rent your e-mail address without your expressed permission.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. Soyring will not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily.
Opting Out
From time to time, Soyring will send newsletters, surveys, and/or other information via e-mail. If you prefer not to receive any or all of these communications, you may opt-out by following the directions provided within the e-mail or by sending a request to info@soyringconsulting.com.
Links to Other Web Sites
Soyring may provide links to various other websites. Soyring assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites that you are able to access through www.soyringconsulting.com. These links to other sites do not imply any affiliation or endorsement of a linked site.
By using our website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you should not use our website.
Featured Resource:
FREE WHITE PAPER
Managing Bottlenecks to Increase Perioperative Efficiency
Download Now
Newsletter Sign Up
Subscribe to “Off the Shelf” to gain valuable insights & actionable ideas for implementing your strategic plans.
